Hello friends, my name is Ashwani Kumar and
as you all know that
friends, I
am selected in II Bank here, friends, in today's
video I am going to tell you the topic here,
brother, brother, you must have seen it in the title and thumbnail,
friends, what I am going to
tell you here in today's video,
brother, a
program has been launched by IIC here, IIC has already
launched a program here, with the
help of which if
you complete that course here, you
enroll in that course and brother,
you complete that course for 1 year, there is a
donation here, that is, it has a duration of one year,
if friends, you
complete that course here, then brother,
directly friends, the
post you get here, brother, you are
given the post of Relationship Manager here
in II Bank, which brother, is a very good
post here and brother,
your salary package here is also
5.5 lakh per annum here.  Your
package is given here, your
starting salary is one year friends,
here is the time period of the course,
friends, in today's video I am going to
tell you in full detail about this course,
brother friends, should you do this course,
should you do this course here
for the future, if you
want to join II Bank directly,
friends, you want to be a part of II Bank here
or directly
you want to take the post of Relationship Manager
in II Bank, then friends, this
course can be beneficial for you,
how can it be beneficial, friends, in today's
video I am going to tell you here,
if friends, you also want to
work in any bank in the private sector, that is,
you want to get a job in a private bank, then
friends, a
link is given below to join the group, so brother
friends, you have to join the group there
because brother friends,
what happens there, I keep bringing new updates
for you there, if friends,
you are
hdfcergo.com, due to this I was also on
leave here, so brother friends, now I am
free here  Yes, you can message me,
you
can share with me through WhatsApp, etc.
Whatever your locations are here, there are many
locations, I have
already put them in my group here,
you
can connect with me there according to your location, and
courses are also conducted for you, brother, I will
also turn on my mobile screen recording and
show it to you, okay, brother, I have done
my mobile screen recording, on
behalf of ICICI Bank, friends, a
course has been launched here, which is friends, a
PO course
of ICICI has been launched here, which
friends, directly provides
you the post of Relationship Manager, in
which brother, here
ICICI has a Manpal University,
they have typed it with it
in Bangalore, friends, this is Manpal University,
you have to go there for three to four months and
after that, friends, you have to complete this course,
friends, it is a campus of two-three months, there is training of three-four months
and brother, it is of three to four months,
friends  On roll, you are provided on the job training here,
you will be posted here in some bank,
your training will be completed here,
check out the II Bank Mainpal Payo program, you have an opportunity to
pursue exciting bank role, okay, you are going to get a
direct relationship
post here, friends, let's
talk about eligibility, in this
friends, if you want to go here, then
brother, you have some
eligibility criteria here, they have
kept it here, first of all friends, your
graduation should be complete here
and brother, your graduation should have 60
plus marks, you should have 60 plus
marks here, second
friends, your age should be between 21 years to 28 years,
if you fulfill all these criteria here, then
brother, you have to enroll here, to
enroll friends,
you will get the link below here, you will
easily go here, you
will directly click on the link here, friends, its
here  You will reach the official website,
after that brother, your
aptitude test is completed here, the
assessment test is done, you have to
fill it here, after that
you have an interview here and brother,
after that you directly reach
Manipal University, friends, the
fee kept here is from ₹
70000 to ₹ 70000 plus something, its fee here is
included GS, you
can pay it here in installments also or
friends, if you want that brother, you have to
pay it together, then brother,
you can easily pay it here in one go,
friends, it depends on you in what
way you want to pay it here,
friends, now the conclusion comes out here
that whether you should do this program,
you should pay ₹ lakh or not,
brother, I will tell you,
first of all friends, you have to decide whether
you have that much money.
You have ₹1 to ₹1 lakh and
you have 1 year's time. First of all,
you have to decide this. If yes, then you
can go. Secondly, listen to one more thing, if
you want to come into the banking sector, then
first of all, friends,
start with sales here. Gain experience of one to two years.
You will have to do sales for one to one and a half years. If you go
anywhere,
you will
get the post of Relationship Manager. You will have to do sales in that too.
You get a
job in sales in every bank, in the private
sector. If you go to any bank,
you will have to do sales 100%.
Friends, there is no operation program,
you will be given access to the Relationship Manager.
You will also be told there that
you should do sales. And brother, I am talking about
its PO program, whether
you should do it or not. So, brother, if
you have time and secondly, friends,
you have money of ₹1 to ₹1 lakh, then
friends, you can easily do this program
if you have even one of these two
things.  If it is not there then brother I will 100%
say that brother, do not do it at all, you should do one thing,
take a job in any bank in the banking sector, in sales, in whichever
private bank you get a job, you should take a
job there and brother, give it one to two years,
after that switch the bank, you
also get a credible increment in salary and brother, your position is
also raised here,
if you get a promotion in one to two years then it is
well and good, if it does not happen then you should
change your bank, there,
whichever other bank you go to, brother,
your promotion there, brother, there are
chances of getting a promotion soon, okay
friends, this is my
opinion here because brother, I have also
not done any course etc., I have
directly given an interview in II Bank here
and brother, I have been
selected here directly, you can also get it,
brother, if you are hdfcfund.com, we are
easily providing you our
templates,
secondly friends, the biggest thing you will get here is  There is an
opportunity, we are conducting an interview for you.
Thirdly, we
will personally guide you if you
purchase that book from us. The rest is
your choice. If you want to buy, the
link is given below. You
can try it once. Let's
talk about the PO
program. I have already told you that
its fee is ₹100 lakh. If you want to do it,
you will directly get the post
of Relationship Manager. You will have to wait for 1 year.
And only after one year,
you will be given this posting here. So, the
PO program is something like this. It is a 100%
genuine program, there is no such problem.
You 100% get a job. We
guarantee it 100% in this place. So, we will get
you a 100% job.
Friends, I have given you complete details in today's video.
On which topic do you want the next video? Friends, tell me in the comments.
Whatever doubts you have,
you can comment here.
Friends, I will fulfill them for you here.  I will
try my best to do it. Friends, this is all for today.
I have told you the complete details. I hope
you liked this information very much. If you liked the
video then like it. If brother,
you have not yet subscribed to this channel
then brother, go quickly and
subscribe to this channel. See you
till the next video. Take care bye.